recoverytoolbox.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy

**Recovery Toolbox, Inc**. ( _ **Recovery Toolbox**_ ) is committed to maintaining the privacy of the information you share with us. We will never sell, distribute, or rent information about you and your purchases at **Recovery Toolbox**. We will only use the information you share with us for the purposes of enhancing your use of our web site, products, services, or, with your permission, sending you information about our products and services.

Please take a moment to read our privacy policy for a better understanding of the measures we take to protect you and the information you share with us. If you don't find your concern addressed here, please feel free to contact us.

**

The information we collect.

**

If you use a credit card to purchase a **Recovery Toolbox** 's product, the credit card number is encrypted as it passes over the Internet. Your credit card number is not kept or recorded by **Recovery Toolbox** or our computers - it is simply passed through to the credit card company to purchase the course. In this respect, buying a course from **Recovery Toolbox** is similar to a credit card purchase at any store. Neither **Recovery Toolbox** nor the store keeps your credit card number on file.

When you send emails to us asking questions on our website, products, services, or your purchases with us, we obtain the information we need from you to answer your questions appropriately.

When we provide technical supports to you, if necessary, we may collect corrupt data files from you via email or ftp, in order to help you solve the problems in using our products.

**

How we use the information we collect.

** **

Online Orders

**

We use the personal information you supply when placing an online order to complete and ship your order. Your email address is used to send you an order confirmation, the registration information, as well as to alert you to any changes in the availability of the items you ordered.

**

Technical Support

**

We use the personal information you supply when you submit a support question to respond to your question. Your email address is used to send a response from our Technical Support team.

**

Data Files

**

Our email and ftp servers are highly protected so that only our engineers can retrieve files from them. We never transmit your data files via email or ftp unless encrypted with very strong algorithms. Your data files are securely deleted from our servers.

**

Guestbook

**

Information that you provide while using products such as the Guestbook feature is available for all to see. Discretion should be used in entering Personally Identifiable Information within such forums, as it may be collected by third parties. **Recovery Toolbox** does not actively associate the message content entered by our users in the Guestbook with any registration information we may possess. Our server computers will retain this information, however; and it is potentially available for distribution to third parties - most obviously law-enforcement agencies acting under subpoena power, per the terms of our Privacy Policy. We do not use this information to target any advertising to our users, nor is it ever willingly distributed to any third party, such as an advertiser, except if subpoenaed.

**

How to gain access to the information we have on file for you

**

There may be times where you wish to gain access to the information we have on file for you. To receive a copy of this information, please contact us.

**

Notification of changes

**

If, at some point in the future, there is a change to our privacy policy and/or practices that affect your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by email of the relevant changes.

**

Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

**

**Recovery Toolbox** does use the services of third parties, such as e-mail service providers, purchase and order processing merchants and marketing companies that act as independent contractors on behalf of **Recovery Toolbox**. These parties are contractually prohibited from using personally identifiable information for any purpose other than for the purpose **Recovery Toolbox** specifies. We do provide non-personally identifiable information to certain service providers for their use on an aggregated basis for the purpose of performing their contractual obligations to us. We prohibit the sale or transfer of personal information to entities outside of the **Recovery Toolbox** 's affiliates for their use without your approval.

**Recovery Toolbox** may disclose your personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process. **Recovery Toolbox** may also disclose personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Use, End User License Agreement or to protect the safety of our users and the public or under confidentiality agreements with certain third parties which assist us in developing, operating and maintaining **Recovery Toolbox**.

In the event that all or substantially all of **Recovery Toolbox** 's stock and/or assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) are transferred or sold to another entity, or **Recovery Toolbox** (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by, or merged with, another entity, **Recovery Toolbox** may transfer personally identifiable information to the acquiring entity and **Recovery Toolbox** may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without your consent. If, as a result of such a business transition, your personally identifiable information will be used in a materially different manner, you will be given choice consistent with our policy regarding notification of changes.

**Cookies**

Our Website uses **cookie** technology. **Cookies** are short pieces of data generated by a web server that a website stores on a user's computer. Certain pages on our Website may require the use of a cookie for purposes of keeping information you enter on multiple pages together. Cookies also enable us to customize our Website and offerings to your needs and provide you with a better online experience with us. In addition, cookies are used to: 

  * allow registered users to sign in without typing their sign in name each time;
  * measure usage of various pages on our Website to help us make our information; more pertinent to your needs and easy for you to access; and
  * provide functionality such as online orders, **Recovery Toolbox** 's services and other functionality that we believe would be of interest and value to you.

The types of cookies that we use are referred to as **session** cookies and **persistent** cookies. Session cookies are temporary and are automatically deleted once you leave the Website. Persistent cookies remain on your computer hard drive until you delete them. We do not use cookies to gather information concerning your visits to other sites, nor ascertain any personally identifiable information about you apart from what you voluntarily provide us in your dealings with **Recovery Toolbox**. Cookies do not corrupt or damage your computer, programs, or computer files. 

In addition, the service providers we use to serve and host our advertisements, and/or deliver our e-mails, use session and persistent cookies, to track the number of times the Website is accessed and whether the site was accessed from an advertisement. There are no cookies in the advertisement or e-mail. A cookie is placed on your computer only if and when you click on an advertisement or open the e-mail. The cookie generated from the advertisement or e-mail does not contain any personally identifiable information and will remain on your hard drive until you delete it. 

You may set your browser to block cookies (consult the instructions for your particular browser on how to do this), although doing so will adversely affect your ability to perform certain transactions, use certain functionality and access certain content on our Website.
